

Shristy Gupta

M.Tech. Computer Science & Engineering

How to reach me:

Home:

+91 9052112828

Cell:

+91 9052112828

Email:

shristysgupta@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shristy-gupta-868067a3/

Github:

https://github.com/Shristy-Gupta

Course Projects

Blockchain Model

Python, C++, PostMan

- Blockchain Model that creates, validates, and fetches entire chain
- https://github.com/Shristy-Gupta/Blockchain_code

Let's Play Soccer

Python, Pycharm, AI, Min-Max Tree

- Self learner kicker/ goaler finds optimal path to goal using MIN-MAX tree Algorithm
- https://github.com/Shristy-gupta/IITJ_AI2_Lets_Play_Soccer

Reinforcement learning

Python, Pycharm, AI, Q-Learning

- The agent finds optimal route towards rewards with Q-Learning Algorithm.
- https://github.com/Shristy-Gupta/IITJ_AI2_Reinforcement_Lea rning

Personal Profile

I am a software developer with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in creating and designing software.

Education

IIT Jodhpur, Rajasthan

Master of Science in Computer Science

- Enrolled since Sept. 2020 to present
- Taking up specialization courses in blockchain to broaden skill set
- Current CGPA 7.3

Mody University, Rajasthan

Bachelor in Electronics and Communication

- Attended from Sept. 2012 to June 2016
- CGPA 7.89

Amity International School, Gurgaon, Haryana

Intermediate

- May 2011- April 2012
- PCM, Percentage: 89 %

Amity International School, Gurgaon, Haryana

High School

- May 2009- April 2010
- Science, Percentage: 93 %

Career Summary

Software Engineer

Infosys Ltd. Bangalore April 2019 to Sep. 2020

- Xerox, Conduent CRM software.
 Worked on Microsoft CRM and customized as per client needs.
- HTML, JavaScript, JQueryUI, CSS, BootStrap, C#, MVC, Azure

Associate Software Developer

Accenture Pvt. Ltd. Hyderabad Jul. 2016 to April 2020

- Microsoft vendor
- C#, Python, Flask, JQueryUI, REST API, MVC, Azure, Flows, Power BI, SQL, Basic web development

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

C++, Python,C#, JavaScript, HTML/CSS,

Frameworks/Systems:

MVC, Angular, Bootstrap, Visual Studio, Flask

Databases:

MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite

OS:

Windows

Extra Curriculum

Table Tennis, Chess, Basket Ball, Driving, Member of Model United Nations, and Former Member of Infosys Toast-Masters Bangalore.